Guide to the Charles E. Palm papers,1956-1986.
Palm, Charles E. papers,1956-1986.
  - Minnesota Canners' and Fieldsmen's short course - talk, 1958 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - AGFU Honorary Society, 1954-55; 1956-58 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - AIBS-(American Institute of Biological Sciences), 1956-57; 1957-58 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Blauvelt Memorial Award (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Programs-Liberty Hyde Bailey Centennial Celebration, 1958 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Experiment Station Policy- Grants-Problems, 1958 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Animal Husbandry Livestock Committee, 1957 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Commission on Agriculture, 1957 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Professional Standards in Entomology-ESA, 1956-57 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Director Palm - Administrative Group (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Private Consulting Co. - Study, 1956-57 (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - Bailey Hortorium, 1955-57 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - Congratulatory letters received by Director Palm on his appointment as Director of Research & Director of the Ag. Experiment Station, 1957 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - Same as above, 1957 (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - Milk Marketing Data, 1957 (Box 83, Folder 26)
  - Geneva Station, 1957 (Box 83, Folder 27)
  - State College Council, 1957 (Box 83, Folder 28)
  - North Country Farm Tour, 1957 (Box 83, Folder 29)
  - Natural Areas Committee, 1957 (Box 83, Folder 30)
  - Cunningham - thesis report, 1957 (Box 83, Folder 31)
  - Research-talks and articles (Box 83, Folder 32)
  - Cornell Forester's Newsletters, 1925-28 (Box 83, Folder 33)
  - Cornell Forester's Newsletters, 1930-34 (Box 83, Folder 34)
  - Cornell Forester's Newsletters, 1935-37 (Box 83, Folder 35)
  - Cornell Forester's Newsletters, 1938-41, 1951-52 (Box 83, Folder 36)